Hello.
こんにちは
How old are you now?
今いくつですか?
I'm 18 now.
今18です
Pichi Pichi?
ピチピチ?
Don't say "Pichi Pichi" anymore?
ピチピチってもう言わない?
Maybe.
もしかして
I might not say that much.
あんま言わないかも
Are you Gine Gya?
ジネギャですか?
What do you say now?
何て言うんですか今?
picture?
え?
What is it?
何だろう?
You know what I mean, right?
意味は分かるでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
I know, but I might not say it.
分かるけど、言わないかも
What is this?
これは何だろう?
Nice story.
話いいな
The transparency speaks volumes.
透明感が全然喋りますね
But when it comes to designs like this, it doesn't repel water.
でも、こうデザみたいになると、 水とか弾かないからさ
terrible.
やばい
Absorb?
吸収する?
Yeah.
うん
I'll absorb it all.
全部吸収しちゃう
What do you do on your day off?
休みとか何してるの?
On my days off, I like to go shopping and hang out with friends.
休みの日は、 買い物とか、 友達と遊びに行ったり
Or something.
とか
It must have been quite a long vacation period.
結 構休みの期間とか、 長かったんじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going out or anything?
どっか出かけたりとかしてないの?
However, I went to Kyoto with a friend.
でも、友達と京都行きました
It's like walking on a wall.
壁歩きみたいな
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Something like Kiyomizu-dera.
なんか、清水寺のところとか
So, do you really like going to tourist spots?
そういう、やっぱ、 観光スポット行くの好きなの?
No, because I took her with me.
いや、連れたからと
My friend said he wanted to go here,
友達が、なんか、 ここ行きたいって言うので、
I'm called and I go.
呼ばれって行くんだ
You're so kind.
優しいんですね
Are you fukkaru?
ふっかるなの?
I might be a rather boring person.
割とふっかるな方かも
Tai says anything is fine.
何でもいいよって言っちゃうタイ
P.
プ
Are you nervous?
緊 張してる?
a little bit.
ちょっと
You're the type of person who laughs when you're nervous.
緊張すると笑うタイプでしょ
Very correct answer.
大正解
It makes me laugh.
笑っちゃう
You took a big gulp.
大きいもつば飲んだね
Send it.
送りって
I heard you.
聞こえてたよ
Oh no.
やば
Your face is bright red.
顔真っ赤だよ
hot?
暑い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
It's an adjustment.
調整だね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
You can take lots of pictures, right?
いっぱい撮っていいんでしょ
I've been enjoying this.
これ楽しんできたんだけど
Oh no.
やば
terrible?
やばい?
I was like, this is crazy.
こいつやべえってなったよ
No?
ダメ?
Have them stand up for a moment with their whole body in the original position.
全身元に体感一回立ってもらう
This is the first time I've been criticized for my type.
タイプでやばって言われたの初めてなんだけど
Is it dangerous?
やばいか?
A habit of saying.
口癖
Is that so?
そうなの?
Eh.
えー
I wonder what it is.
なんだろう
hard?
辛い?
Like lame noodles.
ラメの麺みたいな
Is it a little sour?
ちょっと酸っぱいんだっけ?
It's delicious.
美味しいよね
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Do you know where the photo is being taken?
今どこ撮られてるか分かる?
Do you understand?
分かる?
this.
これ
You get it.
分かるでしょ
Did you not understand at first?
最初分かんなかった?
Yeah.
うん
I don't understand.
分かんないもんなんだ
hey.
ね
Do you buy the work at a store?
仕 作りはお店とかで買うの?
With smooth fabric.
ツルツルの生地で
It feels nice to touch.
触れ心地いいね
Wasn't it okay to touch it?
触っちゃダメだったの?
I had them make me pants.
パンツにしてもらったのね
Something still...
まだなんか...
What are you touching?
何触ってんの?
Something like that.
みたいな感じ
Suddenly.
急に
I was surprised, but so was I.
びっくりしちゃったんだけど、俺も
That wasn't my intention.
そういう意図じゃなかったから
Is it okay to touch it?
触って大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
But it's hard to see.
でも、見きにくいんだもんね
I was hiding it.
隠してたわ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's a bit adult-like.
ちょっと大人っぽいね
It's smooth.
すべすべだね
It's a lot.
盛りまんだね
It was said for the first time.
初めて言われた
different.
違う
Aren't you acting like a hamster?
ハムスターみたいなもんこしてない?
This is a lot, isn't it?
盛りまんだよね、これね
It's nice to be able to see inside, the other side.
奥が見えるのがいいんだよ、反対側
Don't you think there will be a shadow?
影ができそうじゃないの?
Here.
ここで
Oh no.
やば
What is this?
これは何でしょう?
Like.
みたいな
shadow
影
but.
が
Won't you come with me?
手 ついてこない?
The bottom mouth is talking.
下の口が喋ってるね
Being licked.
舐められて
It's soft.
柔らかいね
Did you spread it?
広げたかな?
Do you touch it yourself?
自分で触ったりする?
When should you touch it?
どういう時に触るの?
When?
どういう時?
Are you horny?
ムラムラするの?
Do you do it with your fingers?
指でやるの?
Do you have a hamster?
ハ ムスターとか持ってる?
It's huge
デカデカしてる
hey.
ね
What part do you touch?
ど の辺触るんだっけ?
The one above?
上の方?
Is this the area above?
上の方ってこの辺?
where?
どこ?
Say there.
そこって言って
I guess I'll hit something.
何か当たるね
I'll paint it a lot.
いっぱい塗っておくね
Do you know how slimy it is?
ヌルヌルしてるの分かる?
This is all mine.
これ自分のだよ、全部
Is this what you see?
この目でいい?
Run up.
走り上げて
Did you paint it?
塗っちゃったの?
It's so creamy.
トロトロだよ
This feels good.
気持ちいいね、これね
It feels good.
気 持ちいいね
Can you touch it right away?
さっそく触ってくれる?
Are you not sleeping?
寝てない?
I'm more suitable.
私の方が適当
I like this.
これ好きなんだ
I'm going to sleep.
寝てちゃうよ
I'll bring it back.
戻すよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It feels good.
気持ちいいね